[{"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.5inches", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Screen Refresh Rate": "144Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "0.3MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Official Standard": "Yes", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "MT6580", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Happyhere"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "1.3MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "1.3MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2200", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"OS": "Android 6.0", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "MT6737", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "1242x2688", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "7MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3174", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Apple Model": "Apple iPhone XS Max", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58 inch", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2408", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6600mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Asus"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.59", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.7", "Display Resolution": "2560x1440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2900", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR,BAR", "LG Model": "V10", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "Language": "Norwegian,ITALIAN,French,German,Russian,Spanish,Polish,English,Portuguese,Turkish,Other"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hotwav"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "1612x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5160", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Hotwav Model": "Note 13 Pro"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2460*1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "8300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"FDD": "B1/B2/B3/B4/B5/B7/B8/B12/B13/B17/ B18/B19/B20/B25/B26/B28(A+8)/B66", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "WP17", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SERVO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Google Play": "Yes", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6737", "Language": "ITALIAN,French,German,Russian,Spanish,Polish,English,Portuguese,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UNIWA"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.84", "Display Resolution": "2280x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4380", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Blackview Model": "BV9900E", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Happyhere"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.4", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1400", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"ROM": "4GB", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "Other", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Feature 6": "Best 2022 Smartphone than for WP19", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SERVO"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "SERVO Model": "12s", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "1080x2408 FHD+", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5380mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"telefony smartfony": "cell phone", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3.2", "Display Resolution": "480X360", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "800", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Other Smartphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Blackberry Model": "9380", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "VGA (480p)", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Resolution": "2340*1080 Resolution", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no", "Doogee Model": "S98 Pro"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Infinix"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7\"", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Turkish,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.8", "Display Resolution": "1080x2280", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "10MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 2.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "5 Selections", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Samsung Model": "S10e", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 240 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 855", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.583 inch", "Display Resolution": "2408 x 1080 pixels", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "13000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Brand Name": "Blackview", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "OSCAL S80"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "1612x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "G5 Mecha", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.43", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"V510N": "Korean Version", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip", "LG Model": "V50S ThinQ", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.15", "Display Resolution": "1792\u00d7828", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3110", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card+1 eSIM"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"battery health": "> 85%", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "Apple iPhone 11", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\u201d", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"OS": "Android 13.0", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "WP22", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "POCO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Charger": "22.5W in-box charger", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "EAC", "Item Condition": "New", "POCO Model": "POCO M3 Pro", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Sony"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.01''", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "23MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2700mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 2.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card,1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"MTK Model": "Helio P20 MT6757", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Sony Model": "Sony", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "1080x540(1080x540)", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Other,Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"OS": "Android 11", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.72", "Display Resolution": "2400*1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperVOOC", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "2G,3G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Processor": "MediaTek Helio G88 Octa-core", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "realme model": "realme c55", "Design": "BAR", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,HD (720p) 30 fps,HD (720p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,EAC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "1080x2460", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "100MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Global Version": "Yes", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.74", "Display Resolution": "2772*1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "144Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4600mah", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "realme model": "Neo", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hotwav"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.26", "Display Resolution": "1520X720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "7500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"4G": "B1/B3/B7/B8/B19/B20", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "IIIF150"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "2460*1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "FlashCharge", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Feature": "Thermal Imaging Camera", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.80", "Display Resolution": "1080x2460", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "10MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "V60 ThinQ", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "8K (4320p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 865", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OnePlus"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Storage": {"ROM": "256G"}, "Memory": {"RAM": "8G"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "3120\u00d71440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Dash Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "GSM,CDMA,WCDMA,CDMA2000,LTE", "NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Optical Zoom": "no", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Oneplus Model": "7 pro", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 855", "CPU Core Quantity": "Octa Core"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.1", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2800", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Dimensions": "142 x 72.5 x 8.1 mm", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Samsung Model": "Samsung Galaxy S5", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "KR(Origin)", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.56", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"OS": "Android 13.0", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "C36", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "9800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Watch", "OUKITEL Model": "WP21", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 2.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Radio": "FM Radio", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip,BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio P60", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "800MAH", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "wp27", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "8300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "OUKITEL Model": "WP27", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Video recording resolution": "4K (2160p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Samsung"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "1440x2560", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/White/Gold", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "SAMSUNG Model": "Exynos 8890", "Samsung Model": "S7", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.2", "Display Resolution": "1280x768", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"system": "Android11", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,pse", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio P70", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"OS": "Android 13.0", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Video recording resolution": "4K (2160p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Sony Ericsson"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.2", "Display Resolution": "480x854", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1500", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "no"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/Pink/White", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Design": "BAR", "Sony Ericsson Model": "LT15i", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "HD (720p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7''", "Display Resolution": "1650x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.73\u201c", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen,Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "MIUI 13"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "12 pro", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Model Number": "Redmi 6A", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "NOTE 8", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2712x1220", "Screen Refresh Rate": "144Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi K60 Ultra", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.43", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"feature8": "phones smartphones", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 10S", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G95", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "1560x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5180", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G35", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Snapdragon 778G"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2652*1200", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge,Other", "Charging Power": "100W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES", "Huawei Model": "Nova 11 Ultra"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Dimensions": "164.9mm*77mm*9.0mm", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G25", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2408 FHD+", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "9600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "FlashCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Card Type": "Nano+Nano+microSD", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.35''", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"CPU": "Adreno 512", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "note 7/ 7 pro", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "IIIF150"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "30w"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Dimensions": "176.3X81.8X9.55mm", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67 Inch", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "50W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "Other,3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "MI 10 PRO", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2712 x 1220", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Processor": "Qualcomm Snapdragon 7s", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 13 Pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}]